Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Transvestia
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Transvestia
1982-1988
Bailey 10
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
120 v.; 18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Some individual titles (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
All individual titles paperbound.
Some titles include personal advertisements.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Bisexuals -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Bondage (Sexual behavior) -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Personals -- United States; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Transvestia
  - Transvestite son, c1982; TV_101_ (Box 101-128)
    Scope and Contents
    Label on front cover, partially obscuring printed ttitle: $2 ea. 3 for $5
  - Transvestite call girl, c1982; TV_102_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite lover, c1982; TV_103_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite mistress, c1982; TV_104_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite's desires, c1982; TV_105_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite nurse, c1982; TV_106_ (Box 101-128)
    Price label on front cover: $2.77
  - Transvestite in bondage, c1982; TV_107_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite whipmistress, c1982; TV_108_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite maid, c1982; TV_109_ (Box 101-128)
    Stamp on top egdge: MBI
  - Transvestite bride, c1982; TV_110_ (Box 101-128)
  - Dominant transvestite, c1982; TV_111_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite whorehouse, c1982; TV_112_ (Box 101-128)
  - Shamed transvestite, c1982; TV_113_ (Box 101-128)
    Price label on front cover: Special 2.50, 5 for $10.00
  - Transvestite wife, c1982; TV_114_ (Box 101-128)
    Price label on front cover, partially obscuring printed title: Special $2.50 5 for 10.00
  - Forced transvestite, c1982; TV_115_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite servant, c1982; TV_116_ (Box 101-128)
    Price label on front cover: Special $2.00 each
  - Closet transvestite, c1982; TV_117_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite husband, c1982; TV_118_ (Box 101-128)
  - Black transvestite, c1982; TV_119_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite in chains, c1982; TV_120_ (Box 101-128)
    Price label on front cover, partially obscuring printed title: Special $2.00 each
  - Transvestite's shame, c1983; TV_121_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite heiress, c1983; TV_122_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite athlete, c1983; TV_123_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite sisters, c1983; TV_124_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite lovers, c1983; TV_125_ (Box 101-128)
  - Transvestite harem, c1983; TV_126_ (Box 101-128)
    "Stamp on tope edge: MBN Price label on front cover: Special 2.50, 5 for $10.00"
  - Degraded transvestite, c1983; TV_127_ (Box 101-128)
    "Stamp on top edge: 23 Price label on front cover: Special 2.50, 5 for $10.00"
  - Transvestite showgirl, c1983; TV_128_ (Box 101-128)
  - Hollywood transvestite, c1983; TV_129_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite's torment, c1983; TV_130_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite teen, c1983; TV_131_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite in jeans, c1983; TV_132_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite seductress, c1983; TV_133_ (Box 129-156)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - Hospital transvestite, c1983; TV_134_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite model, c1983; TV_135_ (Box 129-156)
    "Price label on front cover: Special 2.50, 5 for $10.00 Stamp on top edge: 49"
  - Transvestite bridegroom, c1983; TV_136_ (Box 129-156)
    Stamp on top edge: Model Dist.
  - Transvestite doctor, c1984; TV_137_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite in service, c1984; TV_138_ (Box 129-156)
  - Abuse-loving transvestite, c1984; TV_139_ (Box 129-156)
  - Virgin transvestite, c1984; TV_140_ (Box 129-156)
    "Price label on front cover: Special 2.50, 5 for $10.00 Stamp on top edge: 9 1984"
  - Transvestite tv star, c1984; TV_141_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite hooker, c1984; TV_142_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite French maid, c1984; TV_143_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite in ropes, c1984; TV_144_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite quarterback, c1984; TV_145_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite rock star, c1984; TV_146_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite husband, c1984; TV_147_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite nurse, c1984; TV_148_ (Box 129-156)
    "Price label on front cover, slightly obscuring title: $2.00 ea. Stamp on top edge: 31"
  - Transvestite bride, c1984; TV_149_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite stewardess, c1984; TV_150_ (Box 129-156)
    Stamp on top edge: 42
  - Transvestite teacher, c1984; TV_151_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite model, c1984; TV_152_ (Box 129-156)
  - Degraded transvestite, c1984; TV_153_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite mistress, c1984; TV_154_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite seduction, c1984; TV_155_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite movie star, c1984; TV_156_ (Box 129-156)
  - Transvestite hooker, c1985; TV_157_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite in leather, c1985; TV_158_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite in chains, c1985; TV_159_ (Box 157-188)
    Stamp on bottom edge: [Mo]del Dist.
  - Transvestite teacher, c1985; TV_160_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite in bondage, c1985; TV_161_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite buddy, c1985; TV_162_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite call girl, c1985; TV_163_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite, RN, c1985; TV_164_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite stud, c1985; TV_169_ (Box 157-188)
    "Price label affixed to front cover: 38 $3.95 Covers detached"
  - Transvestite nympho, c1985; TV_170_ (Box 157-188)
    Back cover detached
  - Transvestite senator, c1985; TV_171_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite quarterback, c1985; TV_172_ (Box 157-188)
  - Licking her balls, c1985; TV_173_ (Box 157-188)
  - Sucking her cock, c1985; TV_174_ (Box 157-188)
  - Big tits, hot cock, c1985; TV_175_ (Box 157-188)
  - The lady has balls, c1985; TV_176_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite mania, c1985; TV_177_ (Box 157-188)
    Stamp on top edge: 2
  - Transvestite secretary, c1985; TV_178_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite housewife, c1985; TV_179_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite next door, c1985; TV_180_ (Box 157-188)
  - Ballsy lady, c1986; TV_181_ (Box 157-188)
  - The lady's big cock, c1986; TV_182_ (Box 157-188)
    Price label on front cover: $2.00 ea
  - Cock, balls and tits, c1986; TV_183_ (Box 157-188)
  - His girlfriend's hot cock, c1986; TV_184_ (Box 157-188)
  - Mark's big tits, c1986; TV_185_ (Box 157-188)
  - Transvestite actress, c1986; TV_186_ (Box 157-188)
  - Boss lady's big cock, c1986; TV_187_ (Box 157-188)
  - Taking her cock, c1986; TV_188_ (Box 157-188)
  - Her huge meat, c1986; TV_189_ (Box 189-220)
  - Sucking her dick, c1986; TV_190_ (Box 189-220)
  - She had balls, c1986; TV_191_ (Box 189-220)
  - 10 inch she/male, c1986; TV_192_ (Box 189-220)
  - Transvestite bus driver, c1986; TV_193_ (Box 189-220)
  - Transvestite in heat, c1986; TV_194_ (Box 189-220)
  - Studs in pink panties, c1986; first printing 1981; TV_195_ (Box 189-220)
  - Transvestite biker, c1986; TV_196_ (Box 189-220)
  - Lady Mike, c1986; TV_197_ (Box 189-220)
  - Panty Panter, c1986; TV_198_ (Box 189-220)
  - Silk and lace, c1986; TV_199_ (Box 189-220)
  - Panties with bulges, c1986; TV_200_ (Box 189-220)
  - Transvestite marine, c1986; TV_201_ (Box 189-220)
    Price label affixed to front cover: $3.95
  - "Transvetite [sic] star Spine title: Transvestite star", c1986; TV_202_ (Box 189-220)
    Stamp on bottom edge: 1
  - Transvestite fantasy, c1986; TV_203_ (Box 189-220)
  - Cross-dressed submissive, c1986; first printing 1981; TV_204_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV hustler, c1987; TV_205_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV recruit, c1987; TV_206_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV fantasy, c1987; TV_207_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV call girl, c1987; first printing 1982; TV_208_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV evangelist, c1987; TV_209_ (Box 189-220)
  - Queen of the soaps, c1987; TV_210_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV dream, c1987; TV_211_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV submissive, c1987; first printing 1981, under title "Cross dressed submissive"; TV_212_ (Box 189-220)
  - The lady has balls, c1987; TV_213_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV for hire, c1987; TV_214_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV waitress, c1987; TV_215_ (Box 189-220)
  - Transvestite mistress, c1987; first printing 1982; TV_216_ (Box 189-220)
  - She-male's torment, c1988; TV_217_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV in training, c1988; TV_218_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV show-girl, c1988; TV_219_ (Box 189-220)
  - Transvestite whipmistress, c1988; first printing 1982; TV_220_ (Box 189-220)
  - TV vamp, c1988; TV_221_ (Box 221)
  - That was no lady, c1988; TV_222_ (Box 222)
  - TV starlet, c1988; TV_223_ (Box 223)
  - Transvestite whorehouse, c1988; first printing 1982; TV_224_ (Box 224)